<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<export>
  <help>
    <row>
      <title>Shoutbox</title>
      <text><![CDATA[Shoutbox allows forum members to communicate with each other in an easy to use way. It is similar to a chat-room, but does not require Java, Flash or any other browser dependency! The Shoutbox is updated real-time, meaning any new Shouts someone makes will appear on everyones page at once, you do not need to refresh!<br /><br /><strong>General Features</strong><br /><ul><li>Each member can have their own preferences such as "Hide Refresh Button" or "Disable <em>Enter Key</em> from sending the shout" (shouts can only be sent via the actual button instead, useful for large paragraph shouts!);</li><li>If a member hovers their mouse over the corner of the <strong>global</strong> 'shout area', a double arrow appears. If a member clicks and drags that double arrow, they can resize the Shoutbox to their liking! <em>Please note this feature is for the global shoutbox only</em></li><li>Ability to use Smilies and BBCODE if the administrator allows them.</li></ul><br /><strong>Quick Commands</strong><br />Shoutbox has several Quick Commands that can be used to make certain actions perform in a faster way, here is a list that explains how to use them properly:<br /><ul><li>/announce [Announcement Text] - This will update the announcement in your Shoutbox without having to go to the Admin CP</li><li>/archive - Launches the Shoutbox Archive window (only if member has permission to view it!)</li><li>/ban [name] - This will ban a member from the Shoutbox (only moderators with correct permissions can use this command)</li><li>/moderator member [id|name] - This will launch the appropriate moderator options for that particular member</li><li>/moderator shout [id] - This will launch the appropriate moderator options for that particular shout</li><li>/prefs - This will launch the Preferences window</li><li>/prune [x] - This can be used by only those that have ACP access and will prune all shouts older than [x] days. If no number is entered, a security message will pop-up so you do not accidently wipe the whole shoutbox. /prune 0 will remove all shouts.</li><li>/refresh - This will refresh the Shoutbox (useful if you have your refresh button hidden)</li><li>/unban [name] - This will unban a member from the Shoutbox (only moderators with correct permissions can use this command)</li></ul>]]></text>
      <description>Contains informations on how to use the features included in the shoutbox, like the quick commands.</description>
      <position>1</position>
      <app>shoutbox</app>
    </row>
  </help>
</export>
